[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2006"]}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "In a nutshell, what is this all about?", "question_tokens": ["In", "a", "nutshell", ",", "what", "is", "this", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well, I was diagnosed with cancer in 2006, and I used cannabis as a last resort to heal myself and was able to stabilize myself.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "diagnosed", "with", "cancer", "in", "2006", ",", "and", "I", "used", "cannabis", "as", "a", "last", "resort", "to", "heal", "myself", "and", "was", "able", "to", "stabilize", "myself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "All of you, you've all got children?", "question_tokens": ["All", "of", "you", ",", "you", "'ve", "all", "got", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "You have a 2-year-old I think, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "a", "2-year-old", "I", "think", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "The obvious question say well you can't take cannabis and take care of your 2-year-old child on your own, can you?", "question_tokens": ["The", "obvious", "question", "say", "well", "you", "ca", "n't", "take", "cannabis", "and", "take", "care", "of", "your", "2-year-old", "child", "on", "your", "own", ",", "can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "I completely disagree with that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "completely", "disagree", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "What is your dosage?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "dosage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "I like to eat like maybe half of a cookie, one whole cookie is a little too much for me, depends on the strength.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "to", "eat", "like", "maybe", "half", "of", "a", "cookie", ",", "one", "whole", "cookie", "is", "a", "little", "too", "much", "for", "me", ",", "depends", "on", "the", "strength", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Do you feel a physical and mental benefit from taking cannabis?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "a", "physical", "and", "mental", "benefit", "from", "taking", "cannabis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Why do you feel that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "feel", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Because I was real sick, and they put me on these -- a lot of medications and I started consuming cannabis and they had to do surgery.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "was", "real", "sick", ",", "and", "they", "put", "me", "on", "these", "--", "a", "lot", "of", "medications", "and", "I", "started", "consuming", "cannabis", "and", "they", "had", "to", "do", "surgery", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "So, it reduced -- it reduced the pain?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "it", "reduced", "--", "it", "reduced", "the", "pain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "And it also reduced anxiety, you believe?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "also", "reduced", "anxiety", ",", "you", "believe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "And you all found that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "all", "found", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "And this comes to the central knob of this whole debate for me anyway, which is -- is cannabis, marijuana, is it any different in terms of the potential harm to a parent, to a mother, to a wife, to anybody than alcohol?", "question_tokens": ["And", "this", "comes", "to", "the", "central", "knob", "of", "this", "whole", "debate", "for", "me", "anyway", ",", "which", "is", "--", "is", "cannabis", ",", "marijuana", ",", "is", "it", "any", "different", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "potential", "harm", "to", "a", "parent", ",", "to", "a", "mother", ",", "to", "a", "wife", ",", "to", "anybody", "than", "alcohol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Do you think it's less harmful, more harmful, the same?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "less", "harmful", ",", "more", "harmful", ",", "the", "same", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "No, it's less harmful.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "less", "harmful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Knowing that, would you be happy for your kids to take cannabis from teenage years?", "question_tokens": ["Knowing", "that", ",", "would", "you", "be", "happy", "for", "your", "kids", "to", "take", "cannabis", "from", "teenage", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Well, I want to address one thing a moment ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "want", "to", "address", "one", "thing", "a", "moment", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "You call it coming out of the closet then?", "question_tokens": ["You", "call", "it", "coming", "out", "of", "the", "closet", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Secret marijuana use?", "question_tokens": ["Secret", "marijuana", "use", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "But what are the downsides that you have to be careful of?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "are", "the", "downsides", "that", "you", "have", "to", "be", "careful", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "You have to be careful, just like any prescription drugs, we keep it very safe, locked away from our daughter.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "be", "careful", ",", "just", "like", "any", "prescription", "drugs", ",", "we", "keep", "it", "very", "safe", ",", "locked", "away", "from", "our", "daughter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$6.5 million"]}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "$", "CD", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "By the way, why are you known as that?", "question_tokens": ["By", "the", "way", ",", "why", "are", "you", "known", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, I was one of the first women to come out of the closet from the corporate sector and not only that but I had a magazine, that I built $6.5 million company.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "one", "of", "the", "first", "women", "to", "come", "out", "of", "the", "closet", "from", "the", "corporate", "sector", "and", "not", "only", "that", "but", "I", "had", "a", "magazine", ",", "that", "I", "built", "$", "6.5", "million", "company", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "And you must be thinking -- no disrespect you must be thinking if this carries on being legalized all over America, this is the biggest ka-ching your business is ever going to see, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "must", "be", "thinking", "--", "no", "disrespect", "you", "must", "be", "thinking", "if", "this", "carries", "on", "being", "legalized", "all", "over", "America", ",", "this", "is", "the", "biggest", "ka-ching", "your", "business", "is", "ever", "going", "to", "see", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "This is the green rush.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "green", "rush", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "What do you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I say that you need to educate your children.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "say", "that", "you", "need", "to", "educate", "your", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Could you make edible cannabis, right?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "make", "edible", "cannabis", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "ACHADO: Yes, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["ACHADO", ":", "Yes", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "So, what do you make?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "I make cookies.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "make", "cookies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Any variety?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "variety", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Anything and everything you can do.", "answer_tokens": ["Anything", "and", "everything", "you", "can", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "I mean, how has it worked?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "has", "it", "worked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "What was the preconceived view and what did you come out with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "preconceived", "view", "and", "what", "did", "you", "come", "out", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I mean, I think the preconceived view for me when I went to this place is that it was going to be, you know, a little sleazy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "the", "preconceived", "view", "for", "me", "when", "I", "went", "to", "this", "place", "is", "that", "it", "was", "going", "to", "be", ",", "you", "know", ",", "a", "little", "sleazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Were you surprised how easy it was to get a medical marijuana license?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "how", "easy", "it", "was", "to", "get", "a", "medical", "marijuana", "license", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Yes, it's pretty -- it's pretty simple.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "pretty", "--", "it", "'s", "pretty", "simple", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California", "United States"]}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", ":", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "And in terms of the overall debate, has your view about the marijuana debate changed at all?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "overall", "debate", ",", "has", "your", "view", "about", "the", "marijuana", "debate", "changed", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "I mean, when you look at a state like California where -- and the dispensary that I was in is the largest dispensary in the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "when", "you", "look", "at", "a", "state", "like", "California", "where", "--", "and", "the", "dispensary", "that", "I", "was", "in", "is", "the", "largest", "dispensary", "in", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "And also, you know, I would assume as I've just interviewed one of these pot moms with a thriving business, it will create a whole new world of jobs anyways, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "also", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "would", "assume", "as", "I", "'ve", "just", "interviewed", "one", "of", "these", "pot", "moms", "with", "a", "thriving", "business", ",", "it", "will", "create", "a", "whole", "new", "world", "of", "jobs", "anyways", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "What is the reality of that war?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "reality", "of", "that", "war", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "The reality of that war is very, very dangerous communities and is a nightmare for law enforcement.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "reality", "of", "that", "war", "is", "very", ",", "very", "dangerous", "communities", "and", "is", "a", "nightmare", "for", "law", "enforcement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "So, David Evans, I mean, you know, that's all undeniably true and you wish to continue to criminalize marijuana, why?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "David", "Evans", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "all", "undeniably", "true", "and", "you", "wish", "to", "continue", "to", "criminalize", "marijuana", ",", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Well, first of all, it's not undeniable true.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "undeniable", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Evans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "If it's no more harmful, why not legalize it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "it", "'s", "no", "more", "harmful", ",", "why", "not", "legalize", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Piers, you're very poorly informed on the dangers of marijuana.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "you", "'re", "very", "poorly", "informed", "on", "the", "dangers", "of", "marijuana", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "You're painting a very apocalyptic picture here, Mr. Evans, have you taken marijuana yourself?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "painting", "a", "very", "apocalyptic", "picture", "here", ",", "Mr.", "Evans", ",", "have", "you", "taken", "marijuana", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Yes, I smoked pot in college, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "smoked", "pot", "in", "college", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Evans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Evans"]}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Neill, your reaction to all this?", "question_tokens": ["Neill", ",", "your", "reaction", "to", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Piers, I think most of your listeners know that the information that Mr. Evans is giving us right now is false.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "think", "most", "of", "your", "listeners", "know", "that", "the", "information", "that", "Mr.", "Evans", "is", "giving", "us", "right", "now", "is", "false", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Neill"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "The very dark, gloomy picture he was painting?", "question_tokens": ["The", "very", "dark", ",", "gloomy", "picture", "he", "was", "painting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "And from everything that you have gleamed in the making of the documentary over the last year, as you say, a very intensive study you've done on this, is there any logical scientific backed reason why if tobacco and alcohol are legalized, marijuana should not be legalized?", "question_tokens": ["And", "from", "everything", "that", "you", "have", "gleamed", "in", "the", "making", "of", "the", "documentary", "over", "the", "last", "year", ",", "as", "you", "say", ",", "a", "very", "intensive", "study", "you", "'ve", "done", "on", "this", ",", "is", "there", "any", "logical", "scientific", "backed", "reason", "why", "if", "tobacco", "and", "alcohol", "are", "legalized", ",", "marijuana", "should", "not", "be", "legalized", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "I really can't find that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "ca", "n't", "find", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "What are we doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "we", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "This country is already seriously medicated.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "country", "is", "already", "seriously", "medicated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sanjay"]}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "I mean, what do I tell my 12-year-old who says to me, hey, dad, I thought marijuana was bad for you and they are talking about legalizing it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "do", "I", "tell", "my", "12-year-old", "who", "says", "to", "me", ",", "hey", ",", "dad", ",", "I", "thought", "marijuana", "was", "bad", "for", "you", "and", "they", "are", "talking", "about", "legalizing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "WP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ",", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Let me go to Sanjay.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "go", "to", "Sanjay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Sanjay, what is your reaction to how Samuel says there?", "question_tokens": ["Sanjay", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "how", "Samuel", "says", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WRB", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Look, I mean, he's taking a very safe path here.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "he", "'s", "taking", "a", "very", "safe", "path", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Samuel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "Do you think it should be a schedule one substance?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "should", "be", "a", "schedule", "one", "substance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "See, to that to me sounds absolutely ridiculous.", "answer_tokens": ["See", ",", "to", "that", "to", "me", "sounds", "absolutely", "ridiculous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "So you would decriminalize all drugs?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "would", "decriminalize", "all", "drugs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "No, I wouldn't make them legal.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "make", "them", "legal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "There would have to be some kind of misdemeanor, because what am I going to do -- tell my children is marijuana and heroin is as safe as an aspirin?", "question_tokens": ["There", "would", "have", "to", "be", "some", "kind", "of", "misdemeanor", ",", "because", "what", "am", "I", "going", "to", "do", "--", "tell", "my", "children", "is", "marijuana", "and", "heroin", "is", "as", "safe", "as", "an", "aspirin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "So you would fine people but you wouldn't imprison them.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "you", "would", "fine", "people", "but", "you", "would", "n't", "imprison", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Sanjay, I don't know if you touched at all, Sanjay, your documentary, but in terms of the way America is now trying to legislate this, what do you think is the most sensible course of action?", "question_tokens": ["Sanjay", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "you", "touched", "at", "all", ",", "Sanjay", ",", "your", "documentary", ",", "but", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "way", "America", "is", "now", "trying", "to", "legislate", "this", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "is", "the", "most", "sensible", "course", "of", "action", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "It's extraordinary, Piers, if you think about it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "extraordinary", ",", "Piers", ",", "if", "you", "think", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sanjay"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Is there scientific research that supports the theory, if you're under 25, it could have more effect on you emotionally, psychologically that when you're over 25?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "scientific", "research", "that", "supports", "the", "theory", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "under", "25", ",", "it", "could", "have", "more", "effect", "on", "you", "emotionally", ",", "psychologically", "that", "when", "you", "'re", "over", "25", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "The most definitive data has revolved around two areas.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "most", "definitive", "data", "has", "revolved", "around", "two", "areas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 518, "question": "I mean, aren't we being irresponsible to our children to set them up to have another thing out there to get more dysfunctional and have more problems emotionally?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "are", "n't", "we", "being", "irresponsible", "to", "our", "children", "to", "set", "them", "up", "to", "have", "another", "thing", "out", "there", "to", "get", "more", "dysfunctional", "and", "have", "more", "problems", "emotionally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Don't we have a responsibility?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "we", "have", "a", "responsibility", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "I think we do a responsibility.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "do", "a", "responsibility", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "What are the key conclusions that you personally have drawn about the marijuana debate?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "key", "conclusions", "that", "you", "personally", "have", "drawn", "about", "the", "marijuana", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "Well, that we're going about it all wrong.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "we", "'re", "going", "about", "it", "all", "wrong", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "What is the argument you've heard against what you think that has made the most sense to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "argument", "you", "'ve", "heard", "against", "what", "you", "think", "that", "has", "made", "the", "most", "sense", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I haven't really heard any that make sense.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "really", "heard", "any", "that", "make", "sense", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "You think all the arguments are kind of based on traditional views of I just don't like drugs, full stop?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "all", "the", "arguments", "are", "kind", "of", "based", "on", "traditional", "views", "of", "I", "just", "do", "n't", "like", "drugs", ",", "full", "stop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "RENIER: Yes, I think we've sort of carried of this tradition of this war on drugs where all drug dealers are bag and drug dealers are evil and we should treat them as such by throwing them into jail.", "answer_tokens": ["RENIER", ":", "Yes", ",", "I", "think", "we", "'ve", "sort", "of", "carried", "of", "this", "tradition", "of", "this", "war", "on", "drugs", "where", "all", "drug", "dealers", "are", "bag", "and", "drug", "dealers", "are", "evil", "and", "we", "should", "treat", "them", "as", "such", "by", "throwing", "them", "into", "jail", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "How do you tackle the easing of legislation perhaps with marijuana with the harder stuff?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "tackle", "the", "easing", "of", "legislation", "perhaps", "with", "marijuana", "with", "the", "harder", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I think we need to educate the youth of America.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "need", "to", "educate", "the", "youth", "of", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Is there a coherent argument that all drugs should be legalized and controlled?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "coherent", "argument", "that", "all", "drugs", "should", "be", "legalized", "and", "controlled", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I personally can't see any reason why that shouldn't be on the table.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "personally", "ca", "n't", "see", "any", "reason", "why", "that", "should", "n't", "be", "on", "the", "table", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "This morning?", "question_tokens": ["This", "morning", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Only on set.", "answer_tokens": ["Only", "on", "set", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Is it going to happen?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "going", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Is that a definite?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "definite", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "RENIER: Look, if it doesn't, I will pack my bags and move and you'll never see me again.", "answer_tokens": ["RENIER", ":", "Look", ",", "if", "it", "does", "n't", ",", "I", "will", "pack", "my", "bags", "and", "move", "and", "you", "'ll", "never", "see", "me", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "I should be confident?", "question_tokens": ["I", "should", "be", "confident", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130816pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "How many could you use?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "could", "you", "use", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "Two or three.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "or", "three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]